[
	{
	"question":
		{
			"prompt":"Both fighters fought hard and showed ___.",
			"optionA":"grim determination",
			"optionB":"strong determination",
			"optionC":"harsh determination",
			"rightOption":"a"
		}
	},
	{
	"question":
		{
			"prompt":"Our 25th wedding anniversary is an ___ .",
			"optionA":"auspicious moment",
			"optionB":"auspicious occasion",
			"optionC":"auspicious gathering",
			"rightOption":"b"
		}
	},
	{
	"question":
		{
			"prompt":"___, we need to put aside â‚¤4,000 for the party.",
			"optionA":"As a conservative guess",
			"optionB":"As a conservative forecast",
			"optionC":"As a conservative estimate",
			"rightOption":"c"
		}
	},
	{
	"question":
		{
			"prompt":"We ___ lifestyle as we were unemployed.",
			"optionA":"had a frugal",
			"optionB":"had a careful",
			"optionC":"had a tight",
			"rightOption":"a"
		}
	},
	{
	"question":
		{
			"prompt":"The car screeched ___ and two men jumped out.",
			"optionA":"to a stop",
			"optionB":"to a halt",
			"optionC":"to an end",
			"rightOption":"b"
		}
	},
	{
	"question":
		{
			"prompt":"Since they had a fight at school, they ___.",
			"optionA":"have been sworn competitors",
			"optionB":"have been sworn rivals",
			"optionC":"have been sworn enemies",
			"rightOption":"c"
		}
	},
	{
	"question":
		{
			"prompt":"I'd been in ___ with toothache all weekend",
			"optionA":"excruciating pain",
			"optionB":"agonizing pain",
			"optionC":"maddening pain",
			"rightOption":"a"
		}
	},
	{
	"question":
		{
			"prompt":"I was ___ his incompetence to my manager",
			"optionA":"highly tempted to report",
			"optionB":"sorely tempted to report",
			"optionC":"greatly tempted to report",
			"rightOption":"b"
		}
	},
	{
	"question":
		{
			"prompt":"He ___ but only by working 72 hours a week.",
			"optionA":"makes a living gaining",
			"optionB":"makes a living salary",
			"optionC":"makes a living wage",
			"rightOption":"c"
		}
	},
	{
	"question":
		{
			"prompt":"Workers at the plant are threatening ___.",
			"optionA":"industrial action",
			"optionB":"industrial force",
			"optionC":"industrial activity",
			"rightOption":"a"
		}
	},
	{
	"question":
		{
			"prompt":"After school he ___ errands for his father.",
			"optionA":"races",
			"optionB":"runs",
			"optionC":"rushes",
			"rightOption":"b"
		}
	},
	{
	"question":
		{
			"prompt":"His leaving the company comes ___ to me.",
			"optionA":"as a perfect shock",
			"optionB":"as a deep shock",
			"optionC":"as a total shock",
			"rightOption":"c"
		}
	},
	{
	"question":
		{
			"prompt":"In my first week in charge everything ___.",
			"optionA":"ran smoothly",
			"optionB":"ran easily",
			"optionC":"ran calmly",
			"rightOption":"a"
		}
	},
	{
	"question":
		{
			"prompt":"___ do you expect to see in the next decade?",
			"optionA":"What enhancements",
			"optionB":"What advances",
			"optionC":"What upgrades",
			"rightOption":"b"
		}
	},
	{
	"question":
		{
			"prompt":"After ___ , we decided not to go through with it.",
			"optionA":"deliberate consideration",
			"optionB":"cautious consideration",
			"optionC":"careful consideration",
			"rightOption":"c"
		}
	}
]